（我们合众国人民）
（美属萨摩亚大学
索尔古德曼）
- Yeah.
什么事？
Do you have
any idea what time it is?
你知道现在几点了吗？
Watched pot never boils, Francesca.
心急吃不了热豆腐 弗朗西斯卡
It's been an hour.
已经一个小时了
You've got a lobby
full of people out here,
现在大厅里挤满了人
已经8点了 我要下班了
and at eight o'clock,
I am done.
I don't care if the building
burns down,
就算整栋楼着火也无所谓
我要回家了
I'm going home.
Wow, you and your work ethic.
你也太没职业道德了！
Did I ever tell you
how indispensable you are?
我跟你说过你有多不可或缺吗？
没有吗？
No?
还要多久 索尔？
How much longer, Saul?
You know what? I can't say.
其实我也说不准
So pass along
my sincerest apologies
请帮我向客户致以最真诚的歉意
and tell 'em I'm swamped.
告诉他们我忙得不可开交
Everyone can hear you
bouncing that thing.
所有人都能听到你砸墙的声音
That's the sound of thinking.
这是思考的声音 你应该抽空试试
You should try it sometime.
（金伯莉韦克斯勒
对詹姆斯摩根麦吉尔）
（解除婚姻关系申请书 无子女）
Yeah?
什么事？
What are you waiting for?
你还在等什么？让她进来
Send her in.
NETFLIX 原创剧集
How's it coming?
怎么样？
Good.
还可以
Did you get the mayonnaise?
你买到蛋黄酱没？
Well, here's the thing,
事情是这样的
they didn't have Duke's,
and I really like Duke's.
那里没有公爵牌子的
但我非常喜欢公爵的
But they didn't have it,
which is a bummer. So...
可是他们那里没有 真扫兴
所以…
I dunno.
我说不好
Think this'll work?
你觉得这个能行吗？
I mean, technically, it isn't
actually mayonnaise, but...
严格来说这并不是蛋黄酱 但…
Yeah,
对
technically, I don't think
this is mayonnaise.
严格来说 我觉得这不是蛋黄酱
But close, right?
但很接近 对吧？
What do you think?
Should we give it a shot?
你怎么想？
要不要试试？
I dunno. What do you think?
我说不好
你怎么想？
Yeah.
对
Let's give it a shot.
我们试试吧
["Escape
老天
Oh, my gosh.
I don't know.
It's as close as I could get.
我说不好
我就只能做到这个程度了
Cissy, garnet and gold!
I see it plain as day.
茜茜 石榴红和金黄色！
明摆着！
Plus, they're really
beautiful, Cissy.
而且卖相真好 茜茜
Ah, the red ones could
maybe pass for garnet.
红色的那些或许说得上是石榴红
But the "gold" ones
are just regular yellow.
但金黄色的那些不过是普通的黄色
Well, the minute I saw them
I said, "FSU!"
我一看到就心想“我勒个去”
Besides, gold food coloring?
再说了 可食用金粉？
June, did you
ever even hear of that?
-朱恩 你听说过这东西吗？
-没有 听起来很贵
No! Sounds expensive.
And if they even
make such a thing,
如果真有这种东西
you'd probably
get flipper-hands
那或许人类会因为接触化学物质
长出鳍足
from all the chemicals
they'd put in it.
Well...
反正我就只能做到这种程度了
This is as close
as I could get, anyway.
- Oh, it's perfect, Cissy.
- Thank you.
很完美了 茜茜
- Oh, my gosh.
- Ah, this is all so beautiful.
-一切都太美了
-看起来真不错
- Everything looks amazing.
- Looks delicious.
Oh, I forgot spoons. Sorry.
看起来很好吃
Well, let me tell you
about epoxy--
-我来跟你们说说环氧树脂
-环氧树脂变黄
Epoxy yellows.
You hit it
with enough sunlight...
-如果有足够的日晒…
-他说得对
- No. Well--
- He's right.
- Wait, no.
- No, he's right.
If you just use
a dark enough floor--
如果地板的颜色足够暗…
Guys, I'm telling you,
we're never gonna settle this.
大家听着 这件事永远不会有结论
I've been having this argument
five days a week,
我每周有五天都在跟人争论此事
but now I'm Sweden.
-但现在 我成了瑞典
-是瑞士
- Switzerland.
- You want something to drink?
-想喝点什么？
-冰镇果酒？
- Wine coolers?
- Great. Cissy?
Marvin doesn't
like me to drink.
-茜茜？
-马尔文不想让我喝酒
Cissy, we're gonna
get a wine cooler
down you one day.
茜茜
我们总有一天
要让你喝上一杯冰镇果酒
That was fun.
刚才的聚会还挺有意思
Yeah. That was fun.
对 是挺有意思的
- Yep.
好
Yep.
Yep!
好！
Yep.
That's it right there.
就是那里
Good job, guys.
干得漂亮 各位
"Peter the Great
is buried inside me."
彼得大帝就葬在我体内
-"Find me in..."
- What did she say?
-她说什么？
-我们要互相帮忙
We're gonna
help each other.
Boy, you gotta be in shape
to be on this show.
老天 要上这档节目
总得管理一下身材吧
You sure do.
肯定的
Lotsa running.
经常有跑动
Yeah.
对
You think they ever ran
with the bulls on this show?
这档节目播过人们跟公牛一起跑吗？
Like, in Spain?
在西班牙的时候？
Not that we've seen,
I don't think.
我们没看到过 应该没有
Maybe it's too dangerous.
或许那样太危险了
What do you think?
你怎么想？
Maybe.
或许吧
-好
-开始了
Oh, I thought the potato salad
worked out great.
我觉得土豆沙拉很不错
- You think?
- Yep.
-是吗？
-对
Huh.
Looks like rain again.
貌似又下起雨来了
Yeah. Does.
对 确实是
Oh, hey, they opened
a new Outback
嘿 卫星海滩那边
开了一家新澳美客牛排
down in Satellite Beach.
- You wanna go Friday?
- Sure.
-周五要不要一起去？
-好啊
- It's a date.
那就说定了
（棕榈海岸洒水公司）
Yes. Yes.
好
I don't want to not buy
her toys, but I also...
（金韦克斯勒
产品目录与宣传册）
（灌溉新视野）
Could you tell me
the flange diameter
能告诉我212-17\H型号的
安装盘直径是多少吗？
of 212-dash-17-backslash-H?
Great.
很好
And does that come in
a three-inch riser,
那这个型号的立管是8公分
还是只有5公分？
or just the two-inch?
Great.
很好
ABS or PVC?
ABS还是PVC材质？
Oh. Great.
很好
- Hi.
-嗨
We're gonna
sing at 5:00.
我们要5点钟唱歌
Oh. Great.
很好
Let me see.
我看看
（生日快乐！）
That's cute, June.
好可爱 朱恩
I'll pick up the cake
after lunch.
午饭后我去取蛋糕
Do you remember what kind
of ice cream Tammy likes?
你还记得泰米
喜欢什么口味的冰激凌吗？
Uh... geez, no.
-老天 不记得了
-好吧
Yeah. So maybe...
What do you think?
或许…你怎么想？
Vanilla?
香草还是草莓？
Or strawberry?
Ooh.
Um...
They're both good.
-都很好吃
-我知道 对吧？
I know, right?
- Five o'clock.
- Okay, great.
-五点钟
-好 没问题
No,
nobody makes it that long.
不 没人会造那么长的
Well, I mean, because--
I mean, think about it.
我是说 因为…你想想看
It's got to fit
in the truck, right?
那东西得放进卡车里
那要怎么放得进去 如果…
So, how's it gonna fit
in the truck if--
Well, yeah, but nobody makes
a truck that long, so...
对 但没人制造那么长的卡车 所以…
Safe to say.
这么说比较保险
Okay. Well, sorry
we couldn't be of service.
好的 很抱歉我们不能为你提供服务
So...
whatever happened to crack?
可卡因到底怎么了？
How come you never hear
about it on the news anymore?
怎么再也从新闻上听不到它了？
Did everybody just all decide
to stop taking it?
所有人突然一致决定戒毒吗？
What's the drug that
makes you dance around
吃了让人跳舞
往嘴里塞奶嘴的药叫什么来着？
and put a pacifier
in your mouth?
- Ecstasy.
- Ecstasy!
-摇头丸
-摇头丸！
That's the big one now.
I think that they have--
这玩意现在很火…
Yeah. That's the big one.
对 相当火 我妹妹闺蜜的儿子？
My sister's best friend's son?
Oh, my God...
老天
But I don't understand
the pacifier.
但我不明白奶嘴
他们为什么都需要奶嘴呢？
Why would
they all need pacifiers?
Like, don't you think
if you ran a store
如果你经营一家商店
and some teenager
came in your store
一个十几岁的孩子过来买奶嘴
and tried to buy a pacifier,
don't you think
you'd call the police?
-你不觉得该报警吗？
-对
- Yeah.
- Pbht! I sure would.
-我肯定会报警
-绝对的
- Absolutely.
- Whatcha eating?
你在吃什么？
Tuna salad.
金枪鱼沙拉
I made it with Miracle Whip
instead of mayonnaise.
我用奇妙酱做的 没用蛋黄酱
- Hmm.
- I use almond butter instead of pean--
我用杏仁酱…
（开启PEX管材激动人心的新篇章）
Mm.
When I woke up
this morning,
我今早醒来后
guess what was in
my living room.
猜猜我在客厅看到了什么
A freaking exercise bike.
一辆健身单车
Yeah. I can't believe
he got that for my birthday.
对
他居然送我这个当生日礼物
Hold on a second.
等一下
Palm Coast Sprinkler,
watering your world since 1978.
棕榈海岸洒水公司
自1978年期浇灌你的世界
Please hold.
请稍等
Yep?
什么事？
金 3号线上有一个叫
维克多圣克莱尔的人找你
Kim, there's
a Viktor St. Claire
for you on line three.
Kim?
金？
Uh, yep. Okay.
好 知道了
Yeah. So, what do you
think about that?
对 你怎么想？太没礼貌了
That's pretty rude.
What brand is it?
什么牌子的？
I don't care who made it.
我才不在乎是什么牌子
I don't care
if it's Megatron 3000
我不在乎那是一辆麦格隆3000
还是价值400万美元
or worth $4 million.
I'm gonna ride it
straight back to the store,
我要直接骑回店里退掉
and guess what he's gonna get
for his next birthday.
你猜他下次过生日会收到什么礼物？
Some hair regrowth serum,
一瓶生发血清 我一定会嘲笑他
and
I'm gonna laugh at him.
Yeah.
对
Kim Wexler.
我是金韦克斯勒
Hey, Kim.
嘿 金
You know who this is?
你知道我是谁吗？
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
看来你是听出来了
Uh, that receptionist of yours,
你的前台不是那种
爱偷听电话的人吧？
is she the type to listen in?
- No. - Good.
-不是
-那就好
Okay.
好的
So, how's Florida
been treating you?
你在佛罗里达州那边过得如何？
I'm catching you
between hurricanes, I hope.
希望我没在飓风天打给你
Kim, you there?
金 你在吗？
What do you want?
你想怎样？
I don't--
I don't want anything.
我什么都不想
I just...
我就是…
It's been a while, you know?
好久没联系了 对吧？
Just-- I'm thinking
it's been a while,
我刚意识到很久没跟你联系了
and, um, might be nice
to catch up.
聊聊近况或许会比较好
- "Catch up." - Yeah.
聊近况？
对 我今早思绪万千
My mind was wandering
this morning. I was just...
也没专门去想某一件事
就是一些很随意的想法
Not thinking anything
in particular.
Just random thoughts.
And, bam,
it suddenly occurred to me
it's been six years.
然后砰的一下 我就想到你了
已经过去六年了
I mean, Jesus.
老天爷
I, I couldn't believe it.
我真是不敢相信
I thought you might wanna know
I'm still alive.
我想着你或许会想知道我还活着
Yep.
好
I'm still out here,
still getting away with it.
我还蹦跶着呢
还没被逮起来呢
The feds couldn't find
their own ass
那些联邦警察就是睁眼瞎
with both hands
and a proctologist.
You shouldn't be calling me.
你不该打给我
Oh, hey! You're awake!
嘿！你醒了！
You shouldn't be calling.
你不应该打给我
Why not?
What, am I tying up the line
为什么不能？我是妨碍你谈一单
重要的灌溉买卖了吗？
for important
irrigation business?
- I mean, come on, Kim. Say something.
拜托 金 说点什么
You can call me an asshole,
yell at me.
骂我混蛋 怎么骂都行
Just let me know
you've still got a pulse.
让我知道你还喘着气就行
Just say something.
说话啊
You want me to say something?
你想让我说话？
Yeah.
对
You should turn yourself in.
你应该去自首
Do what?
做什么？
You heard me.
你听到我的话了
I don't know what kind of life
you've been living,
我不知道你过着什么生活
但肯定不怎么样
but it can't be much.
Said the pot to the kettle!
真是五十步笑百步！
What-- That is--
你真是好意思啊 对我说教？
That is really rich, you--
You preaching to me?
See, you have no idea
what I did or didn't do, okay?
听着
你不知道我做了什么
或者没做什么 好吗？
A-And why don't you
turn yourself in,
你怎么不去自首呢？
seeing as how you're the one
既然你良心难安 对吧？
with the guilty conscience,
huh?
What-- What is stopping you?
是什么在拦着你？
Fring's in the ground.
福林死了
Mike's in the ground.
Lalo's in the ground.
麦克死了 拉罗显然也死了
Apparently.
You don't have to hold back
on my account.
你不必为了我犹豫不决
They can only hang me once.
So-- So go ahead.
他们只能绞死我一次 所以去吧
Spill your guts!
Put on your hair shirt,
see what it gets you!
说出你的心声！
穿上你的刚毛衬衫 看看会怎样！
Why--
为什么…
Kim, why are we even
talking about this?
金 我们为什么要聊这个话题？
We're both too smart to throw
our lives away for no reason.
你我聪明绝顶
不该无缘无故丢弃自己的生活
Just...
I just... I only wanted to...
我就是…
我只是想…
Kim.
金
Kim?
Kim.
-金
-我很高兴你还活着
I'm glad you're alive.
- Yeah?
什么事？
Time to sing!
该去唱歌了！
Okay.
好的
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
祝你生日快乐
♪ Happy birthday, dear Tammy ♪
祝你生日快乐 亲爱的泰米
♪ Happy birthday to you ♪
祝你生日快乐
（阿拉斯加）
（阿尔伯克基）
I can't leave before
the judge dismisses you.
I'll make sure they're aware.
我会让他们知道
记住了 法官跟你说话时
Now, just remember
to sit up straight
and listen carefully when
the judge addresses you.
一定要坐直认真听
Stay attentive and engaged.
保持专心和专注
Even if you're not so sure
what's going on, don't show it.
即便你摸不清楚状况
也不要表现出来
All right. Come here.
好了 过来
- Tuck your shirt in for me, will you?
- Okay.
-把衬衣塞进去 好吗？
-好
You gotta look good
for the judge.
你得在法官面前看起来精神点…
Because of your record...
因为你的前科 法官可能…
想拿你杀鸡儆猴
Kim?
金？
Hi, Cheryl.
嗨 雪柔
I'm out front.
我在门口
（萨拉曼卡离开后不久
我和吉米共同谋划 开始了长期）
（意图抹黑）
（豪沃德哈姆林）
（人品的行为）
（为了谋取私利）
（我们制造了）
（他有毒瘾的假象）
（头部中枪 豪沃德）
（当即死亡）
（按照命令 我开车去福林家）
（我被准许回到家中后）
（那里已经布置成自杀）
Howard was murdered?
豪沃德是被人谋杀的吗？
Why?
为什么？
He was...
他…
in the wrong place
at the wrong time.
在错误的时间去了错误的地点
Where's his body?
他的尸体在哪？
I don't know.
我说不好
And the police?
那警察呢？
Will they search again?
他们会重启搜索吗？
They'll search.
他们会的
I don't think they'll find him.
但我觉得他们不会找到他
Cheryl, he...
雪柔 他…
It-- it all happened
in an instant.
一切…
一切都是瞬间发生的 他没…
And he didn't--
he didn't suffer.
他没受罪
"He didn't suffer."
他没受罪？
The lies you two made up.
你俩编造的那些谎言
The picture you painted.
你们描绘的景象
That's all he is now.
他现在就是这样的人了
That's all anybody remembers.
大家就只会记住这些
I want to change that.
我想改变这一情况
What happens now?
然后呢？
Will you be tried?
你会接受审判吗？
Will you go to jail?
你会去坐牢吗？
I don't know.
我说不好
You're a lawyer, right?
你是律师 对吧？
You're a--
A great one, Howard said!
还是个厉害的律师 豪沃德这么说的
How could you not know?
你怎么会不知道？
Bernalillo County
has my affidavit.
我向伯纳利欧县法院提交了书面证词
It's up to
the district attorney
whether to prosecute.
要不要起诉 地方检察官说了算
And she may not.
她或许不会
Why?
为什么？
There's no physical evidence.
因为没有物证
No remaining witnesses
other than my ex-husband,
除了我前夫 没有其他的目击证人
assuming he's still alive.
假设他还活着的话
I could sue you in civil court.
我可以去民事法庭告你
I could take
everything you've got.
我可以夺走你的一切
Yeah.
对
Why are you doing this?
你为什么要这么做？
Oh, God!
老天！
（投资报告）
Passwords. Passwords...
密码
Hmm.
A hat man.
带帽人
（自由奔跑 卢斯蒂
生于1991年 卒于2004年）
Holy shit.
天啊
Nothing to see here.
这里什么都没有
Move on.
走开
Look at this bullshit.
瞧瞧这糊弄人的玩意 瞧啊
Look.
Look. What would you call this?
你会叫这玩意什么？
I'd call that...
我会叫…我不知道 叫什么？
I dunno, what?
Would you call that
a fish taco?
你会叫这玩意鱼肉塔可吗？
有谁会叫这玩意鱼肉塔可吗？
Could anybody
call this a fish taco?
I mean, legally?
Stop waving that thing at me.
-货真价实的？
-别挥来挥去的了
Look at this!
你看啊
There's one piece
of goddamned pollock
里面就一小块鳕鱼肉
还不如我拇指尖大呢
no bigger than
the end of my thumb.
Now, how can you
even call that a--
-怎么能叫这东西…
-我该做点什么吗？做什么？
Like am I s'posed
to do something?
What do you want me
to do about it?
我想让你仔细看看
告诉我你看到了什么
Well, I want you
to look inside there
and tell me what you see.
Huh? W-Would you
or would you not
你会不会把这玩意
卖给毫无疑心的公众？
sell this to
an unsuspecting public?
Why do you persist
in ordering fish
我们离大海两千多公里
你干吗要吃鱼？
when we're 1,400 miles away
from the nearest ocean?
Because it's on the menu,
all right?
因为菜单上有 好吗？
Because I live in the 21st
goddamn century, all right?
因为我生活在21世纪 好吗？
Mm.
And this?
This is some bullshit.
就这玩意？简直是糊弄人
I'm telling you,
I got half a mind
to go on back over there
听好了 我都有点想回去那里
使劲揍谁…
and smack somebody
in their face there.
C14 C14 你那边的家庭纠纷怎么样？
（申请书签名）
（金伯莉韦克斯勒）
Yes!
好的
What do you think?
怎么样？很不错吧？
Pretty great, right?
Yeah, it's, um...
对 是很…
Yep.
好
I just need your printed name
and signature.
我需要你的印刷体签名和签名
So, Florida.
所以…
佛罗里达
Florida, Florida, Florida...
Why there?
为什么去那里？
- I guess--
- It doesn't matter.
-可能是…
-无所谓
Doesn't have to make sense.
没必要非讲出什么理由来
Hey, I gotta tell you,
I think you're gonna regret
嘿 我得告诉你
我觉得你以后肯定会后悔
没拿胜佰德的那份钱
not taking your share
of the Sandpiper money.
That'd buy a shitload
of swampland.
然后买一大片沼泽地
I will, um,
我会…
file these tomorrow.
我会明天提交文件
All right. Well.
好的 祝你以后过得好 金
Have a nice life, Kim.
Hey, Sweetcheeks,
who do we got next?
嘿 小甜心 下一个客户是谁？
我们大赚一笔吧
Let's make some money!
Emilio Koyama!
埃米利奥科亚马！
Where's your paperwork?
-你的资料呢？
-我没有资料
I don't do no paperwork.
He doesn't do paperwork!
他没有资料！
Who cares? Come on, come on.
谁在乎呢？快过来
（索尔古德曼 律师）
（欢迎临时预约）
Hey, yo, could I bum
one of those?
嘿 能借根烟给我抽吗？
Thanks.
谢谢
Mm.
What's up with this shit?
这是怎么回事？
Rainy.
多雨
Yeah. No. It-- It's crazy.
对
真是离谱
It's like bananas,
all this rain.
倾盆大雨
I mean, I thought we were,
like, in a desert, you know?
我们这里不是沙漠吗？
You're a lawyer, right?
你是律师 对吧？
Ah. I recognize you.
我认得你
You defended my buddy Combo.
你曾为我朋友康宝辩护
Christian Ortega.
克里斯丁奥特加 少年法庭？
Juvie court,
stole a Baby Jesus.
他偷了一个耶稣宝宝？
I mean, not like
a real baby, just a--
不是真的耶稣宝宝 就是一个…
教堂外摆的那种东西
You know, one of those things
outside of the church.
- Nativity scene.
- Yeah.
-耶稣诞生景
-对
Knights of Columbus.
哥伦布骑士团
I mean,
what the hell did he even
want that thing for?
他到底要那玩意干吗？
- Huh?
- I mean, I-- I still don't know.
我现在还是搞不懂 白痴
Dumbass.
I told him he could go to Hell
我告诉他偷那种东西可能会下地狱
for stealing something
like that, I mean.
但他有听我的吗？没有
But did he listen to me? No.
But you, you got him off,
like, scot-free. That--
但你 你帮他逃过一劫
让他逍遥法外 那…
That was pretty slick, yo.
真是太厉害了你
Well, tell him I hope
he's keeping his nose clean.
告诉他 我希望他远离毒品
Yeah, yeah, right on.
好 没问题
Absolutely.
肯定的
Ah.
Hey, so, you having all this
expertise and all...
嘿 你明明很会打官司
This guy Goodman?
这个叫古德曼的家伙
He the real deal?
他厉害吗？我是说在打官司方面？
Like, lawyer-wise?
Why do you ask?
问这个做什么？
I got a buddy in there
who's facing some serious time.
我里面有个朋友 他摊上大麻烦了
I mean, not-- you know,
not Baby Jesus-time,
不是偷耶稣宝宝那种麻烦
很大的麻烦
but... but serious.
他需要找个顶级律师
You know, he needs top-shelf
legal representation.
And I tell him that, right?
我这么跟他说的 好吗？
但他在电视上看到了这人的广告
But, you know, he sees this
dude's commercials on TV
and this is where
he wants to go.
所以就想来找他
And I tell him, "Yo, Emilio,
you know, a funny TV commercial
我告诉他：“嘿 埃米利奥 其实
浮夸的电视广告
并不一定代表 你懂的…”
is not a sound basis
for, like, you know..."
I mean, like, would you
go to doctor to do, like,
你会凭着一条浮夸的电视广告
an operation on you in like a--
就去找那个医生
on, like,
your spleen or whatever
on the fact of a funny
TV commercial?
给你的脾动手术吗？肯定不会
No. I mean, come on.
拜托 这能有什么区别呢？
How is this any different?
You know?
Anyway...
无所谓了
Is this guy any good?
这家伙 他靠得住吗？
When I knew him, he was.
我之前认识他时倒是靠得住
（北4街10号）
Hello?
喂？
Hey, uh, Dad?
嘿 爸爸？
It's me. It's-- It's Jeff.
是我 我是…我是杰夫
Jeff? What time is it?
杰夫？现在几点了？
Are you okay?
你没事吧？
Yeah, no, not really.
好吧 我有事
Um, I, uh...
Dad, I got arrested.
爸爸 我被逮捕了
Oh, no.
不是吧 为什么？小杰
What for? Jeffie.
It's like this crazy mistake,
you know?
就是个离谱的错误 好吗？
我出了事故
I mean,
I had an accident, okay?
A, a little fender-bender
type deal, no, no big thing.
小交通事故 没什么大不了的
My foot maybe slipped
on the accelerator,
我的脚或许不小心踩到了油门
或许油门出了问题
or maybe it was
a defective-- I dunno.
我不知道 但这不算大问题
But that's not
the big-deal part.
The big-deal part is,
真正的大问题是 警察认为我…
they think that I, me,
committed a robbery.
他们觉得我犯下了盗窃案
And why would they think that?
-他们怎么会这么想？
-我知道 对吧？
I know, right?
The place
where I had the accident?
我出事的那个地方？
一个喝醉酒的男人？
This guy? This drunk guy?
He comes wandering
out of his house
他从自己家里溜达出来
把警察喊了过去
and flags down the cops,
the, the police, and says,
"Hey, you know, I got robbed!"
他说：“嘿 我家被盗了！”
And sure enough, the police?
警察自然找到了小偷破门而入的证据
They find evidence of, like,
breaking and entering.
And, and, and stuff is missing,
which I did not do.
而且…确实有东西丢了
但不是我偷的
And, uh... yeah. Like that.
还有…
对 就是这样
Well, the police are obviously
barking up the wrong tree.
警察显然抓错人了
Yeah. No shit, wrong tree!
对 可不是嘛 抓错人了
- Wrong, like, forest. - Exactly.
-错大发了
-没错
Because you would never do
something like that,
因为你绝对不会做那种事
对吧 儿子？
would you, son?
对 绝对不会 肯定不会
No. No. No way, man.
Absolutely not.
Uh, when the police
took you into custody,
警察羁押你时
did they find any of this
so-called stolen merchandise?
他们有找到所谓的被盗物品吗？
Was it in your possession?
-东西是你在那里吗？
-没有
- No. - Of course it wasn't.
当然没有 因为你没偷任何东西
Because you didn't
steal anything.
Therefore, since there's
no evidence whatsoever
that you committed any crime,
因此 既然没有你盗窃的证据
I'd say you got nothing
to worry about.
我觉得你没什么可担心的
So, what happens next?
那接下来怎么办？
Breathe deep and sit tight.
深呼吸 耐心等待
我会在午饭前把你捞出来
I'll have you out by lunchtime.
You coming down here yourself?
你要亲自过来吗？
Nah, I think it'll be your mom.
不 你妈妈应该会去
You'll talk to her for me?
-你会替我跟她说吗？
-肯定会
I sure will.
I'll straighten it all out,
no problem.
解决一切麻烦 没问题的
Yeah, okay. Good.
好 那就好
Jeff, you're gonna get
the best legal defense
in the whole wide world.
你会得到全世界最棒的法律辩护
Trust your old man on that.
相信你老爸
Okay, copy that. Sit tight.
好的 知道了 耐心等待
You do that.
一定要这样
Keep your shirt on.
冷静
Hello?
喂？
Gene.
吉恩 亲爱的 你知道现在几点吗？
Gene, Honey,
do you know what time it is?
Oh. Oh, God. That boy.
老天 那小子
He's gonna put me in my grave.
他总有一天会气死我
Marion.
玛丽恩 这就是个误会
It's a mistake, is all.
Getting picked up
for something you didn't do?
蒙冤被捕？任何人都可能摊上这种事
That could happen to anybody.
Yeah, right, anyone.
好吧 任何人 可这不是第一次了
This isn't
the first time, you know.
He's been in trouble before.
他以前就惹过麻烦 老天爷
Oh, Jesus.
- Marion...
- The death of me.
-玛丽恩
-气死我了
He's gonna be the death of me.
-他一定会气死我
-玛丽恩？
Marion. Marion,
it's gonna be all right.
玛丽恩 不会有事的
We'll get him outta there
lickety-split.
我们一眨眼的功夫就能救他出来
I've been
through this before.
我是过来人
不可能一眨眼的功夫就解决
There's nothing
lickety-split about it.
Back when he was living
in Albuquerque?
他当初在阿尔伯克基时
在公开场合醉酒 拒捕
Drunk in public,
resisting arrest,
urinating in
someplace he shouldn't have.
在不该撒尿的地方撒尿？
And me on the telephone
for hours, long distance,
我好几个小时泡在电话上
远在千里之外
费心思为他找保释地点
trying to find him one of those
bail-out places.
I maxed out my Discover card.
我刷爆了自己的发现卡
到现在还没还清
I'm still paying for that one.
Well, money's
not gonna be a problem,
钱不是问题 我会出钱帮你
'cause I'm gonna
help you with that.
No. Gene,
I can't let you do that. No.
不行 吉恩 我不能让你这么做
Sure you can.
Jeff'll pay me back.
你当然可以 杰夫会还我钱
And you don't have to worry
about a bondsman, either.
你也不必担心担保人
Because guess what?
因为你猜怎么着
奥马哈这里根本就没有
In Omaha, they don't have 'em.
All right?
You just walk into the station
好吗？你只需走入警局 支付保释金
and you pay
a straight cash bail.
It's not like
Albuquerque at all.
跟阿尔伯克基那边完全不同
Marion, you still there?
玛丽恩 你还在听吗？
Yeah. Why--
在 为什么…
Why did
Jeff call you instead of me?
为什么杰夫打给你 不打给我？
Well, I think he was scared
at how you'd take it.
他可能是担心你接受不了
Honestly, I was gonna
pay the bail myself,
说实话 我本打算自己去交钱
但我觉得还是家人去比较好
but I think it should be
a family member.
I think that'd be best.
这样最保险了
I'll tell you what, I'm gonna
take a shower, get dressed.
听着 我马上冲个澡 穿好衣服
And you do the same.
你也一样 我会开车过去接你
I'll swing by and pick you up.
We'll get this whole thing
squared away.
我们会解决所有问题
Wh-what about Buddy?
Is he in any trouble?
那巴迪呢？他有遇到麻烦吗？
I don't think so.
应该没有 他为什么会有麻烦？
Why would he be?
I'll see you in about an hour.
我大概一个小时后过去
Yeah, okay. Yeah. Thanks.
好的 谢谢了
** Oh, no, oh ♪
不
-** It's not the things you do ** -** The tide i-- ♪
巨浪…
♪ That tease and hurt me bad ♪
♪ But it's the way you do ♪
-** The things you do to me ** -** Do to me ♪
-** I'm not the kinda girl ** -** I'm not the kinda girl ♪
我不是那种轻言放弃的女孩
♪ Who gives up just like that ♪
-** Oh, no, oh ** -** Oh, no, oh ♪
不
-** The tide is high ** -** The tide is high ♪
巨浪袭来 但我要咬牙坚持
-** But I'm holding on ** -** But I'm holding on ♪
-** I'm gonna be your num-- ** -** I'm gonna be your num-- ♪
我会是你的…
♪ I'm not the kinda girl
Who gives up ♪
我不是那种…
- Marion!
玛丽恩…
♪ Just like that ♪
轻言放弃的女孩
♪ Oh, no ♪
不
Marion!
玛丽恩…
Marion?
玛丽恩？
玛丽恩…
- Oh!
- Hey.
嘿
Hi.
-嗨
-嘿
Oh, hey.
Everything okay?
没事吧？
Oh, yeah. I'm sorry.
不好意思 我应该是忘了时间
I-- I just lost track
of the time.
That's okay.
没事
Uh, you wanna
put some clothes on
你赶紧换衣服 这样我们就能出门了
so that we can get moving?
What do you say?
怎么样？
Uh, you know, well, I, I...
我不想拖累你
I don't wanna slow things down.
I think maybe
you oughta go without me.
或许你还是自己去吧
...partying, minding
my own business.
You are under arrest.
你被逮捕了
I better call Saul!
我最好打给索尔
Hi. I'm Saul Goodman.
嗨 我是索尔古德曼
你知道自己拥有权利吗？
Did you know
that you have rights?
The Constitution says you do,
and so do I.
宪法说你有权利 我也这么说
我认为在被证明有罪之前
I believe that,
until proven guilty,
every man, woman, and child
in this country is innocent.
这个国家的男男女女
包括孩童都是无辜的
- - And that's why I fight for you, Albuquerque!
所以我为你而战 阿尔伯克基！
“有事找索尔”
What's that?
那是什么？
You tell me.
你倒是告诉我
Marion, do you think that's me?
玛丽恩 你觉得那人是我吗？
'Cause it's not.
因为他不是
There never was a Nippy,
was there?
你根本就没有叫尼皮的狗狗 对吧？
What did Jeff tell you?
杰夫跟你说什么了？
Oh, he didn't tell me anything.
什么都没说
Ask Jeeves told me.
询问杰夫斯告诉我的
I typed in "con man"
and "Albuquerque,"
我输入了“骗子”和“阿尔伯克基”
and up you popped, big as day.
你一下子就蹦出来了
What are you doing, Marion?
-你要干什么 玛丽恩？
-不然怎么样？当然是报警
What do you think I'm doing?
I'm calling the police.
Here, lemme help you with that.
给 我帮你
Listen, I think
we're losing sight
我感觉你没有顾全大局 好吗？
of the bigger picture
here, okay?
Jeff is in trouble,
and I wanna help him.
杰夫有麻烦了 我想帮他
He and I sure could use
your support here.
我和他肯定需要你的支持
What did you get my son into?
-你害我儿子惹上了什么麻烦？
-那都是他自找的
- Nothing that he didn't ask for.
Now, listen,
听着 我还是你之前
眼里的好朋友 好吗？
I'm still the good friend
you thought I was, okay?
Jeff understands me,
Buddy understands me.
杰夫理解我 巴迪理解我
And you will, too.
你也会理解我
It's just, you have to, uh,
只是…我们得保持冷静
you know, keep things
on an even keel, all right?
好吗？
- What have you got there?
- Uh...
你手里是什么？
- Put that down.
- Huh...
快放下
Put that down, Marion.
快放下 玛丽恩
Put it down.
放下
Do not do it, Marion.
别这样 玛丽恩
Final warning.
我最后一次警告你
I trusted you.
我曾那么相信你
Marion?
This is Valerie
with Life Alert.
玛丽恩？我是生命警报的瓦莱莉
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
No, Valerie, I'm not okay.
不 瓦莱莉 我有事！
There's a criminal standing
in my kitchen, threatening me!
有个罪犯正站在我家厨房里威胁我！
He's a wanted man,
他是通缉犯 名叫索尔古德曼！
and his name is Saul Goodman!
All right, Marion,
I'm calling the police.
好的 玛丽恩 我这就报警
我马上报警
I'm calling right now.
字幕翻译： 吴春燕